{
    "id": "a8e296d8b35246289b2845795bb9e9aa",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is smarter than ...................",
            "description": "You has the same subject and object form.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He lives on ..................... own terms.",
            "description": "We need a possessive adjective here hence we use his.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "his",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The old woman is quite fond of .................... grandchildren.",
            "description": "We need a possessive adjective here. The words your, my, our, his, her and their are possessive adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you show me ..................... passport?",
            "description": "We need a possessive adjective here. The words your, my, our, his, her and their are possessive adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I know ................... and .................... parents.",
            "description": "A pronoun used an object should be in its object form. Before a noun, we need a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "he, his",
                "him, his",
                "himself, his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my passport. Can you show me .........................?",
            "description": "The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "your's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That purse is .........................",
            "description": "The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That dog of ..................... is always barking at me.",
            "description": "The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "your's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Whose bag is this? It is ......................",
            "description": "The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "her's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When are you going to return the camera you borrowed from ………………………….?",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Does she understand what .................... is doing?",
            "description": "A pronoun used as a subject should be in its subject form.",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What she says or does makes no sense to ………………………….",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}